lyricfind.com 2004-06-04

# LyricFind.com Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy On This Site**

 **What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**  
No personally identifiable information is collected by LyricFind.com or it's affiliates, unless entered by you (such as information collected by CDnow when ordering a CD through us, or subscribing to our mailing list).  [DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.net/) & [Engage Media](http://www.engage.com/), LyricFind's ad serving companies, collect anonymous data profiling the patterns of your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you; no identifying information is collected.  Anonymous clickstream information is collected for every visitor to this site, using cookies and/or IP's. This includes pages viewed, date & time, and browser type. IP numbers are not stored, but are temporarily used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic region. There is no association between this information and a visitor's identity.  To view Engage's Privacy Policy, please visit <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>.  To view DoubleClick's Privacy Policy, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>.

**How is it used?  
**The information is used by Engage to build anonymous behavioral profiles which are written to the Engage Knowledge database -- securely housed at the Engage data center. These profiles are accessed by Engage-enabled web sites to offer you personalized content and promotions, and to target relevant, more interesting ads -- all without knowing your identity. Again, there is no association between an Engage Knowledge profile and a visitor's identity. For more information, [click here](http://www.engage.com/privacy/knowprivacy.htm). 

For users who prefer not to have their web usage information reflected in Engage Knowledge, Engage provides an [opt-out procedure](http://www.engage.com/privacy/koptout.htm).

The information culled by Engage and DoubleClick may also be used to serve more relevant and targeted ads to anonymous users when visiting this or other sites in the DoubleClick or Engage networks.

To opt-out of DoubleClick's anonymous tracking, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are used on this site by both LyricFind.com and its third-party advertisers. The third-party advertisers use cookies to track non-personally identifiable surfing information. LyricFind.com uses cookies to provide personalization and minor user tracking features. Some examples are: Remembering your name & email when posting comments & messages; tracking if you've voted for the poll; and tracking song rankings.

**Mailing List**  
LyricFind.com will not divulge your e-mail address to any third party organization under any circumstances.  This information will be kept confidential at all times.  In the case of advertisements within the newsletter, advertisers will not be informed of any personal information of anyone subscribed to the mailing list.

**Posting**  
In the case of posted requests or messages, LyricFind.com is not responsible for your personal information.  Any information posted tot he public by you is done at your own risk of exposure; LyricFind.com cannot garauntee your privacy under these circumstances.  Please note that, in all cases, all information provided is optional; you are never required to enter any information you do not wish to.

**For more information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail [darryl@lyricfind.com](mailto:darryl@lyricfind.com).
